[
  {
    "question": "Which testing is done without executing the code?",
    "option 1": "Static Testing",
    "option 2": "Dynamic Testing",
    "option 3": "System Testing",
    "option 4": "Sanity Testing",
    "answerkey": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which testing ensures that changes have not affected existing functionality?",
    "option 1": "Smoke Testing",
    "option 2": "Regression Testing",
    "option 3": "Unit Testing",
    "option 4": "Integration Testing",
    "answerkey": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which testing evaluates a system's behavior under extreme load conditions?",
    "option 1": "Smoke Testing",
    "option 2": "Sanity Testing",
    "option 3": "Functional Testing",
    "option 4": "Stress Testing",
    "answerkey": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Which level of testing comes immediately after integration testing?",
    "option 1": "Unit Testing",
    "option 2": "Smoke Testing",
    "option 3": "System Testing",
    "option 4": "Acceptance Testing",
    "answerkey": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a white-box testing technique?",
    "option 1": "Usability Testing",
    "option 2": "Exploratory Testing",
    "option 3": "Path Testing",
    "option 4": "Statement Testing",
    "answerkey": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Which testing focuses on user interface and user experience?",
    "option 1": "Usability Testing",
    "option 2": "Functional Testing",
    "option 3": "Security Testing",
    "option 4": "Performance Testing",
    "answerkey": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following determines whether testing is complete?",
    "option 1": "Entry Criteria",
    "option 2": "Test Case Review",
    "option 3": "Exit Criteria",
    "option 4": "Risk Analysis",
    "answerkey": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which software development model involves frequent iterations and feedback?",
    "option 1": "V-Model",
    "option 2": "Agile Model",
    "option 3": "Waterfall Model",
    "option 4": "RAD Model",
    "answerkey": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which type of testing does not require knowledge of internal code structure?",
    "option 1": "White Box Testing",
    "option 2": "Unit Testing",
    "option 3": "Black Box Testing",
    "option 4": "User Acceptance Testing",
    "answerkey": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which activity is considered a part of static testing?",
    "option 1": "System Testing",
    "option 2": "Walkthrough",
    "option 3": "Unit Testing",
    "option 4": "Integration Testing",
    "answerkey": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What is \"Black Box Testing\"?",
    "option 1": "Testing internal code structure",
    "option 2": "Testing without knowledge of code",
    "option 3": "testing only UI",
    "option 4": "testing security",
    "answerkey": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which tool is commonly used for defect tracking?",
    "option 1": "Selenium",
    "option 2": "JIRA",
    "option 3": "Jenkins",
    "option 4": "Git",
    "answerkey": 2
  }
]